http://www.steiffusa.com/privacy-policy/

Loading... Please wait...
Your privacy at Steiff USA Online Shop
We value the trust you place with Steiff USA Online Shop. Because we respect your privacy, we want you to know how we may use the information we have about you. If you have questions, concerns or feedback about our privacy policy, you may contact us through the following:
E-mail: support@steiffusa.com
Phone (US and Canada) (888) W-STEIFF |  (888-978-3433)
Phone (International) (401) 312-0080
Mail:
Steiff North America Attn: Customer Service/Privacy 24 Albion Rd. Suite 220 Lincoln, RI 02865 USA
Information we collect
We may collect information from you (including your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, credit card information, transaction information such as date and time of purchases and items purchased) when you register on our site, place an order, return and item or make an exchange, receive a gift package, inquire about our services and products, subscribe to our newsletter, sign up for e-mail updates request a catalog, respond to a survey or fill out a form, enter contests or sweepstakes, referred to us through or participate in promotions and events.
Cookies, pixel tags and automated information collection
Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information (such as your IP address, browser type, domain name, etc.). Pixel tags are small image files found on our website pages and in e-mails.
We use cookies and pixel tags to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.
If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders over the telephone or by contacting customer service.
Social media Our website includes social media features , such as Facebook 'Like" or 'Recommend' buttons, Pinterest, Twitter, Tumblr, YouTube, etc. These social media features may require cookies to be set to function properly. These features may also collect personal information such as your IP address and pages you are visiting. These social media features are governed by the privacy policy of the company that provides it.
What do we use your information for?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:
To process transactions (to process and track your order, contact you about the status of your order.Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.
To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
To send periodic emails.The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.
How do we protect your information?
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information. We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. After a transaction, your private information (credit cards) will not be stored on our servers.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
Third party links
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.
Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
Steiff USA Online Shop does not sell products for purchase by children. We may sell products for purchase by adults.
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. In the event that we conduct promotions or contests that allow children under the age of 13 to participate, we will use reasonable efforts to obtain verifiable parental consent before any personally identifiable information is collected.
Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
Our privacy policy  may be updated. If there are changes to our privacy policy, they will be posted on this page.
This policy was updated 5 Nov 2013.
© 2020 Steiff USA Online Shop.
Switch to Mobile View
